{
    "subject": "resource/Saravak",
    "predicate": "property/coordinatesRegion",
    "object": "IR",
    "human_readable": "Saravak coordinates region is Iran.",
    "questions": [
        {
            "score": 0.9181001782417297,
            "question": "Is Saravak a part of Iran?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.6291162967681885,
            "question": "Where is Saravak located?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.5870322585105896,
            "question": "What is the significance of Saravak in relation to Iran?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.5744381546974182,
            "question": "Can you provide more details about the Saravak region?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.5555360317230225,
            "question": "To which country does the Saravak region belong?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.47503942251205444,
            "question": "What are some interesting facts about the Saravak region?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.47464317083358765,
            "question": "Are there any notable landmarks or features within the Saravak region?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.4422321021556854,
            "question": "What type of geographical feature is Saravak?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.41774797439575195,
            "question": "How would you describe the geography of Saravak?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.39905253052711487,
            "question": "Is there any specific history associated with the Saravak region?"
        }
    ],
    "google_pages": [
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Saravak coordinates region is Iran.",
            "html": "dbpedia_1890_0.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=How would you describe the geography of Saravak?",
            "html": "dbpedia_1890_1.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=What type of geographical feature is Saravak?",
            "html": "dbpedia_1890_2.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Are there any notable landmarks or features within the Saravak region?",
            "html": "dbpedia_1890_3.html"
        }
    ],
    "selected_docs": [
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_1890_16.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_1890_23.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_1890_37.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_1890_55.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_1890_73.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_1890_81.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_1890_86.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_1890_87.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_1890_90.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_1890_91.txt"
        }
    ],
    "final_question": "Is true?",
    "responses": {
        "gemma2": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{'output': 'yes'}\n``` \n"
        },
        "llama3.1": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "Here is the structured JSON format with the answer:\n\n```\n{\n  \"output\": \"yes\"\n}\n```\n\nThis is because all the documents mention that Saravak is located in Hamadan, which is a province in Iran. The information supports the triple \"Saravak coordinates region is Iran\"."
        },
        "qwen2.5": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{\n  \"output\": \"yes\"\n}\n```\n\nThe information in the documents supports that Saravak, which is located in Hamadan, Iran, has specific geographic coordinates. Therefore, the statement \"Saravak coordinates region is Iran\" is correct based on the provided context."
        },
        "mistral": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": " {\"output\": \"yes\"}"
        }
    },
    "need_tiebreaker": false,
    "tiebreakers_responses": {
        "qwen2.5:14b": {},
        "llama3.1:70b": {}
    },
    "final_decision": 1,
    "actual_decision": 1,
    "analysis": {
        "stratum": "The Least Popular",
        "topic": "-"
    },
    "errors": {}
}